medicalxpress.com 2011-04-29

# PhysOrg.com : FAQ | Contact Us | Suggest a story idea

## PhysOrg Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At PhysOrg.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. 

PhysOrg.com does not collect any personal information about you when you visit our Web site.   
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using. 

To enhance your experience with our site, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. 

#### PhysOrg Account policy

You may access some of our services by signing up for a PhysOrg Account and providing us with some personal information. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, and choose a password. When you create an account on Physorg.com, certain information that you provide (e.g. nickname) is visible to other users of Physorg.com. PhysOrg does not rent or sell your personal information with other people or nonaffiliated companies except when we have your permission. 

#### Electronic newsletters policy

We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. PhysOrg.com gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. PhysOrg.com will never disclose your name or email address to third parties. 

#### Forums policy

Users of the PhysOrgForum must register separately for these services (free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address. Please, read a separate page for PhysOrg.com Forums usage terms. 

#### "E-mail this to a friend" policy

Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link to a news story to someone else by clicking "Email" link. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only to let the recipient know who sent the email and is not retained by PhysOrg.com in any form. The information is not used for any other purpose. 

#### Children

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

#### Surveys

PhysOrg.com may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party. 

#### Linked Web Sites

We provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites. 

#### Questions?

Updated: **October 6, 2007**
